<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>this is not another mental breakdown.</title>
    <link>https://medik.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on this is not another mental breakdown.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 12:14:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://medik.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>what am I doing</title>
      <link>https://medik.github.io/post/what-am-i-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 12:14:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medik.github.io/post/what-am-i-doing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What am I doing with my life. What current projects am working with at the momet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I got a game development project going on in LÖVE..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am learning Haskell.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am working on a Software Defined Radio solution for SEAM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do have stuff to do&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wasd keyboard</title>
      <link>https://medik.github.io/post/wasd-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 15:52:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medik.github.io/post/wasd-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I bought a new a keyboard recently, it is a MX Green 60% keyboard and it looks like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img later /&gt;
It has different layers you can program. I feel thought that they could make it clearer what these layers are and how you change it. Besides of what I recently mentioned; it is a great keyboard. It made my table look spacier :-)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>https://medik.github.io/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 10:11:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medik.github.io/bio/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I am a 23 year old physics student and currently located in Stockholm, Sweden. My hobbies include learning new programming languages, learning vegetarian recipies, listening on music, reading books and keeping up with current technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, my main operating system is a Mac. Stallman wouldn&amp;rsquo;t approve, but I figured that it won&amp;rsquo;t help what I try to do. I rarely work in Windows and avoids it if I can. For servers and such I usually work with a Linux based distro. 99 per cent of the times it is Ubuntu (yeah Stallman, I know you hate me) and it is stable enough to be called my main server OS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OpenWRT is running on my router. Mostly because of shit and giggles, but as control freak I like to have super duper control of the firewall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xkcd and smbc is my main source of my daily chuckle. My friends are sending me to other pages. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Economist is providing me with weekly insight on what is hapening today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am involved in Stacken where I am currently the Secretary. Stacken is a computer club meant to be a hub for creating new software and learn new technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Python3 is the programming languge where I do all the &amp;ldquo;need today asap etc&amp;rdquo; stuff. Meanwhile my language where I need more type safety and scalability is Java. I hope that Haskell will be my functional programming language of choice in the near future. I don&amp;rsquo;t usually write lowlevel code, but if I have to it would be either Go or C and I am no expert in these two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of things I&amp;rsquo;ve completed so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;programming&#34;&gt;Programming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;loopiaupdate&#34;&gt;loopiaupdate&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;loopiaupdate is a program written in Python that connects to loopia and updates
the ip for a domain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;imgdown&#34;&gt;ImgDown&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ImgDown is a program written in Ruby that is supposed to download image urls if
it match a Regular Expression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;restaurantq&#34;&gt;RestaurantQ&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a program that retrieves the current lunch from Restaurant Q at KTH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also contribute to open source projects such as iputils, qlmarkdown and
hugo-steam-theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On my spear time I trying to learn other programming language. I would say that
I am on beginner level in Haskell, C and Go. My favorite language is Python, but
can also work with Java and C#.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;server-management&#34;&gt;Server Management&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have 10 years experience in Linux environment. To maintain those skills I have
servers with CentOS and Ubuntu running at home trying different setups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;networking-skills&#34;&gt;Networking Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have read CCNA 2009 to 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hi</title>
      <link>https://medik.github.io/post/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 03:16:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medik.github.io/post/test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>