<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>./hack_the_planet</title><link>https://medik.github.io/</link><description>Hacking foo for bar since 1 January 1970</description><atom:link href="https://medik.github.io/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2017 &lt;a href="mailto:medik@knark.io"&gt;medik&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 23:22:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>I got a Mechanical Keyboard Fetish</title><link>https://medik.github.io/posts/i-got-a-mechanical-keyboard-fetish/</link><dc:creator>medik</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently bought a keyboard from WASD keyboards. It is a small form factor keyboard i.e. a keyboard that only contains alphanumerical keys, this is also called a 60 per cent keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WASD Keyboard is a mechanical keyboard manufacturer, and has an online shop where you can choose a form factor and what mechanical switches the keys should consist of. The mechanical switch I chose is designed by the manufacturer Cherry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cherry is a German computer peripheral-device maker that is most known for its mechanical key switches. It has been used in industrial electronics since 1980s until 2008 when keyboards targeted at consumers contained Cherry switches. They are most famous for its MX series, and are distinguished with colors. More information about available mechanical switches and other useful information are at r/mechanicalkeyboards wiki.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chose MX Green witch has an actuation force of 80 cN, this is similar to the Model M which has an actuation force of 90 cN. One can feel a "bump" when pressing down the key, this makes it possible to feel that a key has been pressed without doubt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img alt="http://i.imgur.com/MWn8CnS.jpg" src="http://i.imgur.com/MWn8CnS.jpg"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looks nice, doesn't it? It made my table more spacier than ever :-)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>https://medik.github.io/posts/i-got-a-mechanical-keyboard-fetish/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 23:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hello World!</title><link>https://medik.github.io/posts/hi/</link><dc:creator>medik</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello world!&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid>https://medik.github.io/posts/hi/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 22:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>